<ExplorationEvent>
  <Name>Unexplored cave</Name>
  <PotentialOutcomes>

    <Outcome>
      <Chance>25</Chance>
      <TitleText>Ein Nest!</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>Als sich Ihre Truppen der Höhle nähern, hören sie Geräusche aus dem Inneren.  Sie werfen eine Fackel hinein, um die Tiefen zu erhellen, und erkennen Bewegungen.  Leider hat sich hier ein Ameisenlöwennest niedergelassen!  Wie aus dem Handbuch zünden sie schnell Sprengstoff am Eingang und verschließen so die Bedrohung im Inneren.</DescriptionText>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <TroopsToSpawn>
        <string>Antlion</string>
          <string>Antlion</string>
          <string>Antlion</string>
       </TroopsToSpawn>
       <Image>Encounters/1.png</Image>
       <ConfirmText>Ich hasse diese Viecher!</ConfirmText>
    </Outcome>

    <Outcome>
      <Chance>15</Chance>
      <TitleText>Es ist ein stinkendens Nest!</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>Als sich Ihre Truppen der Höhle nähern, hören sie Geräusche aus dem Inneren.  Sie werfen eine Fackel hinein, um die Tiefen zu erhellen, und erkennen Bewegungen.  Leider hat sich hier ein Ameisenlöwennest niedergelassen!  Um die außerirdische Kolonie im Inneren zu vertreiben, beschlossen sie, Sprengstoff in die Höhle zu werfen.  Die Detonation erschütterte die Erde und verursachte ein Erdloch, das das Gelände noch tiefer in den Planeten einhüllte.  Dadurch wird eine Vielzahl giftiger Gase freigesetzt.  Bald darauf füllt sich die Höhle mit einer stark ätzenden Flüssigkeit.  Den ersten Scans zufolge scheint es sich um einen einzigartigen dritten Wasserstoffzustand zu handeln, H³.</DescriptionText>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <ReplaceWith>Evaporative Wastepit</ReplaceWith>
       <Image>Encounters/2.png</Image>
       <ConfirmText>Niemand erwähnte den Gestank?!</ConfirmText>
    </Outcome>

    <Outcome>
      <Chance>20</Chance>
      <TitleText>It's infested!</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>As your troops approach the cave, they hear a faint sound that comes from inside. Tossing in a flare to illuminate the depths, they see nothing. Initial scans shows it's an entrance to a very massive cave system. After a few dull moments of silence, a horde of antlions suddenly surges forth! They're surrounded!</DescriptionText>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <ReplaceWith>Cave system</ReplaceWith>
      <TroopsToSpawn>
        <string>Antlion</string>
          <string>Antlion</string>
          <string>Antlion</string>
        <string>Antlion</string>
       </TroopsToSpawn>
       <Image>Encounters/3.png</Image>
       <ConfirmText>Lets be Cavemen!</ConfirmText>
    </Outcome>

     <Outcome>
      <Chance>25</Chance>
      <TitleText>Unexpected meeting</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>While exploring the cave, your troops stumble upon some crates and an aged smuggler that introduced him self as Roland. They fashioned a deal with him to provide our colony with food and equipment, in exchange for money in regular intervals.</DescriptionText>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <ReplaceWith>Drop off point</ReplaceWith>
       <Image>Encounters/4.png</Image>
       <ConfirmText>Shady business, i like it!</ConfirmText>
    </Outcome>

    <Outcome>
      <Chance>15</Chance>
      <TitleText>Updated scans</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>While exploring the cave, your troops scanned the underground mineral composition. The results revealed that the planet crust wasn't as rich as the orbital scans initially suggested. Planet scans changed : -0.4 Richness.</DescriptionText>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <ChangeRichness>-0.4</ChangeRichness>
       <Image>Encounters/5.png</Image>
       <ConfirmText>Caves are dark and full of terrors!</ConfirmText>
    </Outcome>

    <Outcome>
      <Chance>25</Chance>
      <TitleText>Updated scans</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>While exploring the cave, your troops scanned the underground mineral composition. The results revealed that the planet crust is in fact richer than the orbital scans had initially suggested. Planet scans changed : +0.6 Richness.</DescriptionText>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <ChangeRichness>0.6</ChangeRichness>
       <Image>Encounters/6.png</Image>
       <ConfirmText>Caves are dark and full of wonders!</ConfirmText>
    </Outcome>

    <Outcome>
      <Chance>10</Chance>
      <TitleText>Scam</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>While exploring the cave, your troops encountered a shady-looking character who claimed to be a cave explorer. He presented an offer, our money in exchange for a map of this cave system which apparently contains a secret room with some old military technology. After the successful transaction, the troops went straight for the secret room to recover the tech. Sadly, it wasn't there. They were scammed by that fat bastard!</DescriptionText>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <MoneyGranted>-250</MoneyGranted>
       <Image>Encounters/5.png</Image>
       <ConfirmText>Was he Fat tho?</ConfirmText>
    </Outcome>
    
  </PotentialOutcomes>
 </ExplorationEvent>